Hello everybody and welcome to another
live where we're using tools like Google
Flow
to help us create videos where we can
communicate our ideas, our creativity,
our emotions, our humor, our questions,
promote a product, promote a service,
communicate our thoughts, anything that
you want. There is a way that you can
use Google Flow
to communicate anything that you want
pretty much. And I'm teaching you the
skill and you run with it and create
with it what you wish. Hello all. Hello
Trash Panda. Welcome in. Welcome in.
As the title suggests, we're creating
prompts. I'm showing you how to create
prompts using Google Flow.
It's Google's AI and that is accessible.
The ground rules are going to be set
right now.
Everybody can access it for free for the
first month.
Let me make myself a little smaller
here.
You can access for for free for the
first month using the Google AI Pro
subscription. See here? $0.
And then it's $20 a month and you can
create 50 videos on Google Flow
and then you can create three more.
50 a month, okay? And then you can
create three more a day on Google
Gemini.
Three more a day on Gemini. So in the
month, you're talking about 140 videos.
Again,
to communicate, it's a tool.
All right, you're going to be able to
communicate your creativity, your ideas,
your questions, your emotions,
anything that you wish
comes to life with Google Flow.
And the engine behind all this is Google
video 3. As you can see here, when you
look at up the plan features,
and I don't make commission off of this.
I'm just showing you what I'm using, all
right? Okay? So this is
the Gemini app is what you get
uh with this and also Flow.
We're signing up for Google AI Pro
specifically for these two apps because
they gave us access to the engine, which
is VO3. VO3 is the engine that makes
these videos work.
So, here in my last live,
last time I did a live here on YouTube
and on TikTok,
we discussed making prompts using
um
a prompt bot, which I created, right?
Let me see if I can find it right there.
The cinema prompt are using JSON format
prompts. So, if you missed that live,
you can go to my YouTube channel, you
can find it. It's the last live before
this one.
So, that is a way that you can create
these prompts using a JSON format cinema
prompter, which I've built here. And you
can access this by going to the link in
my bio.
And if you're here on YouTube, or if
you're on TikTok, also link in bio. You
can find it there, where you can
see all my links, but this one
specifically is right here. It's called
free cinema prompter GPT.
Hello, everybody. Welcome in. Welcome
in.
See who's watching here today. Let's see
our friends watching. We have uh we have
two of our usual friends here that I can
recognize.
Well, let's go ahead and talk about some
videos that you can make. So, I've been
making these videos pretty much for the
past 2 months since it came out. Uh we
have commercials. We have For example,
this this whole place right here, I was
taking
I was taking um suggestions the last
time we we were live
for commercial ideas, for prompts. So,
this is some of the stuff that we
created. Somebody asked to make a Tesla
commercial, so we went ahead and made
this one. Let me play it for you.
So, that was using
the JSON prompt bot that I just showed
you before. I didn't have to type all
this in.
Hello, Abe. Hello.
So, that is the commercial there.
And guys, let me do one more thing here
before we get started.
I got to promote my um my live to the
general group here. We have general
chat. Live now.
This is my Discord server. If you're not
a part of it, this is only for people
that are in my course.
So, we have over 600 members now on the
Discord server.
Did I spell prompts right? Prompts.
Yeah, I did. I'm just making sure. Make
sure the thumbnail looks good.
So, let's go back here to Google Flow.
So, I put that in there now.
All right. So, what do we want to do
here today? So, when you start with
Google Flow, all you have to do is sign
up for, again, the Google AI Pro
subscription. And then you can just go
to google.com and type in Google Flow.
Some people have trouble finding it.
Hello BK. How are you, sir? Hello AI
Skits. AI Skits, what's your Discord
name? I'm I I know you're in the
Discord, right? I think.
I think you are. I'm not sure. I don't
see your badge.
Good. You're good?
How's your How's your um
creation going? You have a pretty good
system.
I am. Yeah, so I don't know your name in
there. I I I think I I know what it is,
but I can't remember.
Uh yeah, you have a pretty good system.
Every time you pump out a video, BK,
your videos are getting nice views.
Whatever you doing, keep doing it.
And you can also
look for other ways
to make more more videos, like using the
JSON bot.
You don't have to type so much. I'm
trying.
All right. So, here we go.
Let's go to Flow again.
He's very helpful. He's awesome, right?
So, I made some videos yesterday. Um and
I was trying it out. It was like a late
live that I did.
Pretty much uh
I went on for like an hour or so.
Let me see here. 1 second, guys. 1
second.
Make sure that I'm I'm over here on
YouTube.
Monitoring the chat. I don't know what
the chat on YouTube is on this. Okay, so
we have chat right here.
All right, yeah. So, we got we're good
over there.
All right, so anyway, I was making some
videos yesterday cuz I went live and I
wanted to try out some of these
characters
in these live videos. So, I made them
with the green screen.
Yes, I Yeah, so Brandy, yeah. All right,
I just wanted to make sure. I thought
that was it cuz I remember clicking on
your profile yesterday and seeing your
videos.
And then I thought I saw those videos
that you shared on the Discord.
So, I connected the two.
Cuz sometimes I don't know for sure.
All right, so anyway, guys, this I want
to show you this video right here
on this live. This is how I made This is
how I made this and this is what it
looks like. So, right now I'm going to
play it for you. Let me get I'm going to
put that guy on the screen that you just
saw, that that lion, all right?
So, let me get myself off the screen
here for a second and I'll bring the
lion in.
It's hard to be the king of the lives,
but I couldn't do it without you guys.
All the likes, the follows, and the
gifts are really appreciated. I see you
tapping that screen. Thank you.
I'll see you guys next time.
All right, so that's how I use that.
Thanks for tapping that screen.
Thanks for getting the the likes moving
over here.
Now, I just did something. When I did
that, I made my
my entire scene here huge on my on my
computer. I don't know how I did that.
But, it works out. It's fine. So, that
was what I used, um Google Flow, okay?
So, let's click on this prompt and see
what happens.
So, essentially, I took a photo of
myself right in front of my camera here.
So, you see what I I have my creator hat
right here.
And I had that shirt on yesterday. So, I
took a photo of myself just like this. I
looked at the camera, snapped it.
And then I put it into Chat GPT and I
said,
uh make this character into a lion with
white fur.
And then it gave me uh with the solid
green screen behind them.
So, that's the prompt I entered into
Chat GPT. It gave me this It gave me
this um right here. It gave me this
photo right here, right?
So, after that,
I typed in character adjust his
headphones, then walks away to the left
of the screen, leaving the screen com-
completely.
Cut to a close-up of his face.
And he says, "I'll see you guys next
time." So, this was the second part. It
was a It was a stitched-up video. So,
you saw that the video was longer than 8
seconds. That's because it was two
different videos that I made.
It took me a few tries. Let's see what
this one
uh tripod shot, no movement, character
completely disappears. Oh yeah, so this
is one of the thing Did you see the new
Flow update? I did see it. I know I put
also notes here.
Let me see what the notes said.
I saw it, but I didn't get to explore. I
I took a screenshot in case I um
to read it later.
Well, you want to tell me about it? Go
ahead, cuz I I forget. I forget what
they added.
Forget what they added. It was something
about um
ingredients to video.
I forget it. I forget what it was about.
Bro, you How do you make 1916 videos? I
don't get that format for Insta.
Oh, yeah. All I did was update upload a
photo.
Hold on one second, guys.
I don't know why this scene is so blown
out.
All I did was up- upload a photo, a 1916
photo into Google Flow.
And then it makes the video landscape,
though. It's not a vertical video. It
looks vertical here, but the black bars
are still on the side.
All you have to do later is when you
download it, download it upscale it to
1080.
And then you're going to crop the sides
up.
Make sense? So, you upscale it, download
it, and then you just bring the sides
in, and that's going to give you a
vertical video. That's how.
Yeah, you upload it with no bars. Yeah,
you just crop it out. Either zoom in or
on your iPhone, you crop it.
So, in this in this one, I wanted the
character to come in and out.
So, for example,
you see how he walks in? Let me show you
again. And I'm going to cut him off real
quick. I just want to show it to you.
See how he comes into the screen? Watch.
It's hard to be the king of the lives,
but I couldn't See how he walked in from
the left? So, this is how I got that
effect to make to to happen. Look.
Tripod shot, no movement, cuz I wanted
this shot to be steady.
Uh
Let me move move this up so you can see
it.
I'm I'm going to read it. I can't move
myself cuz I blew out my screen and I
can't see I can't move this I can't move
myself out of the way now. So, look.
Tripod shot, no movement. Character
completely disappears after the first
frame, leaving only the green screen
background. Then the character walks
into frame from the right wearing the
same headphones and shirt and hat.
Keep the same as the intro. So, keep the
same framing as the intro. Meaning, I
wanted that framing to come back. You
see how he walked out of the screen? At
first, I had to put a image of him. So,
then I asked it to make the image go
away completely. I just have the image
so it knows what it looks like. So, let
me play this for you so you can see it.
See that?
That's exactly what I wanted to happen.
I wanted the image to fade away. I just
gave it as a reference.
Look at that.
So, he completely walks in cuz now he
already knows the character that's in
there. It's hard to be the king of the
lives, but I couldn't do it without you
guys.
So then I extended that frame. You see
how he he kind of
went on to the next sentence right
there?
And that's how this one started.
So
that's how I got that uh video with this
green screen behind them and then I just
removed it after post.
I see what you're saying in the chat
here. Okay, let's see uh up there
updating with the
Yeah, so when you when you left or
right, is it always the character's left
for the person looking at the screen?
Um
yeah, so I would have said right you can
see he comes in from the right.
See, he walks into frame from the right.
That's the right side.
It's
it's when you're looking at the screen.
And then I said, "Here
I said um
he walks
I said to the left of the screen on this
one. Let me see what he does here.
I'll see you guys next time.
All right, maybe I maybe I wanted him to
walk to the left. I'm not sure. But
yeah, this is left. You see how this
left it went left?
I don't know what my thought process
was. Maybe I wanted him to go all the
right and I just said left.
And then this one is coming in from the
right.
So that's the that's the answer for
that.
"When do you normally go on live?"
Johnny on YouTube asked. 3:00 p.m. on
weekdays
except Wednesdays.
And then I sometimes I go live on
Saturdays, but it's not really a
it's not really a schedule. It's whether
I can or not.
Let me answer that on there.
All right.
EST, that's EST time.
What apps do you use for your videos?
And is there any cost?
Yeah, there's a $20 a month cost for
VO3.
It's what I use.
I actually use the $125 a month
cuz I make so many now, but I just I
just signed up like last week literally.
I was using the $20 a month.
But then I found myself running out of
credits. So the the cost is $20 a month.
So I use that.
And then I use ChatGPT to make my first
frames. Like this guy right here was
made in ChatGPT.
Okay, I fixed my window. That was
bothering me. I finally fixed my window.
Now I can see what I'm doing.
Any other questions, folks? Or else
we're going to keep moving here. I'm
going to show you some prompts that
we've been building since the title of
this live is prompting. Let me show you
some baby ones that I baby ones that I
made. It's as Brandy knows, as AI skits
knows, it's hard to make the baby
prompts.
And I tried a few times, man. I tried a
few times and it didn't really work.
Look at this one. This one was uh
let's see.
Uh this one was a mistake. I put a
newborn uh is being is holding
I was typing the prompt and then I had a
I sent it by mistake.
Let me move myself out of the way.
Yeah, I was typing the prompt and midway
I hit enter on my phone.
So, that was a waste. This is what
happened.
Still cool It's still cool, though. He's
taking selfies.
All right. Guys, if you can help me out,
let's try to get to 1,000 likes on this
live.
See if TikTok will push us out a little
more cuz we have uh
we have a
14 people in here. See if we can get to
1,000 likes just by tapping that screen.
It's free.
Talking about free, it's free to tap on
that screen here on TikTok.
All right. Thanks for watching. Johnny
on YouTube. I'm also streaming this on
the other platform that I just said the
name. I can't be saying that name too
much cuz it's TikTok will give me a
warning. All right. So, here we go.
Here's the one that I typed. A newborn
baby is sitting in his his hospital bed
wearing an infant
um
hospital hat. Selfie camera extended arm
vlog style. He says, "Hey y'all, it's my
It's It's your boy El Bambino. Today's
my birthday. Can I get a like in the
comment? Thank you." So, it didn't like
the vlog style situation. So, I cuz the
video didn't work out. Watch how it
Watch the blooper here.
It just makes baby gargling noises.
I'll try JSON. Maybe I'll try it.
I have a JSON bot that I created. Let's
see if I Let's see if it works with the
baby stuff.
There you go.
That's the bot if you want to use it.
It's in my bio.
Uh let's see. Another one. I think this
one worked. This one worked.
So, I did the same thing, but I removed
the extended vlog style thing. I don't
know. This one did not work. This one
did not work.
Let's see. Hey y'all, it's your boy El
Bambino. Today is my birthday.
So, see that? No captions. Right here I
wrote still gave me captions. Still gave
me captions.
And I think the one that worked is this
one right here. This one's the one that
worked.
Hey y'all, it's your boy El Bambino.
Today is my birthday. Can I get a like
in a comment? Thank you guys so much.
All right. That one worked. The reason
why I did it again right here
and it failed with the captions was
because I accidentally um
Oh, not accidentally. When I said the
vlog camera, it actually made him hold
the camera cuz I wanted to have See
holding a selfie camera vlog style? I
wanted him to kind of hold it like this
like he's talking to you. And then it
gave me the vlog camera like right, you
know, you see it holding the camera. So,
I tried it again. But then I was I
settled for this one here.
I settled for this one right there.
Sound like gargling goop.
That did not
sound like gargling goop.
Did I miss much? No, I just started. You
didn't miss much. Just started.
Uh so, that is the one that worked out.
Uh this one, what is this one about?
Gargling noises again or whatever we
think it sounds like. What do you think
this sounds like? I'll play it again.
It's your boy X. Oh, not this one. This
one this one this one.
I don't know what it sounds like right
here.
No, where is the one that sounded like
uh
Anyway.
Anyway, I'm too I'm past that now.
I'm I'm over that noise. This is the one
that I I
I did and I put it in my Discord group,
which is
uh the Joker one. I'll play that.
Where is the doctor? I want to ask him
why he's so serious.
So, the prompt for this was this. And
also
by saying no captions, it doesn't really
matter. It still gives you the caption.
Oh, look, we got 2,500 likes. Thank you,
guys.
Appreciate it.
How do we get consistent characters and
backgrounds with custom photos of models
and locations?
How do we get consistent characters and
backgrounds
with custom photos? Well, the custom
photo is what the consistent is the
consistency lies on.
So, if you have a a photo that shows a
model or a character in the background,
that's your consistency. Just use that
same photo for different back for
different videos. The starting point.
So, if you're Where are you generating
these photos? That's the thing. When you
say custom photos, where are you
generating these photos?
Cuz maybe that's the place I need to
worry about having different angles of
the same person in the same background.
Not on VO3. VO3 is just a continuation
of that photo. So, for consistency, you
got to worry about where you getting
that photo from.
Here's another one, a baby.
Did I read this one out to you? Okay,
the prompt said a newborn baby with his
face painted like the Joker is sitting
up in the hospital bed, moody lighting,
cinematic environment. He says, "Where's
the doctor? I want to ask him why he's
so serious."
He gives uh a maniac laugh. No captions.
He has teeth, by the way. Look at him.
He's got teeth from day one.
And then here is uh it's the You know
all the videos are are just landscape. I
wanted to stack them up top and bottom.
So, a newborn baby with his face painted
like the Joker staring at a mirror,
over-the-shoulder shot, just a cinematic
shot over the shoulder.
And these were typed by me. I didn't use
a bot or anything for these. You have to
You have to know how to type these
prompts.
Um it's very simple. You just have to
keep keep trying.
What app am I using? I'm using this app
right here called Google Flow.
And if you want to learn the
step-by-step, you can watch all my
videos here on TikTok. I have everything
that I teach in my course. The course is
a package bundle for a price.
But I have everything that's on the
course pretty much everywhere on my
TikTok.
So, it's just a it's a way of bundling
everything for a price. It's in my
course step-by-step. You can get that
and I'll show you that.
Google Flow is what I'm using. 20 bucks
a month.
Here's the video of the
over-the-shoulder shot of the baby
staring into the mirror.
That's it. Are you using Are you doing
Bigfoot vlogs? I I did my share of
those. Yes.
Here, I have a bunch of Bigfoot vlogs
right here.
Here.
Let's play some of that. Let's look at
some of these prompts here.
I'm a little gassy.
And by the way, where did I leave my
Stanley Tumbler?
Ay, Dios mio.
I'm a little gassy.
I remember this one. This one was done
on June 19th at the height
at the height at the height of the
height of the Bigfoot vlogs.
June was the month of Bigfoot vlogs.
They're still popular, but June was more
popular. You know what's popular now?
This trampoline ones. Oh, let's
the last
2 weeks. It's fading now. The trampoline
vlogs are the trampoline videos are
fading now.
Let's play this one here and I'll show
you how I how I I I wrote it.
So, he falls. Are you posting these
videos on YouTube? Um
these VO3 videos, no. I'm posting this
video here
showing you how to do them on YouTube.
These videos I just do it for the lives.
And also for my TikTok account, I have
some that I use.
Uh for example, I post them all here. I
don't post them on YouTube, no. I post
them on TikTok.
All my views are zero for some some
reason.
It's glitchy.
Let's refresh it.
There you go. Now the views are
uploaded.
So, this one I posted on TikTok, see?
Are the
Are the ones ringing the doorbell?
I don't have are there ones ringing the
doorbell? No. No, I don't I don't I
don't have any of those. This is the
prompt that I use for this guys.
This is a prompt. I'm trying to make
this a prompt workshop so people can
understand how to write prompts and I
keep going over all the things. So, for
a historic setting, a mammoth goes up on
a trampoline made of natural resources
like trees, vines, and stretched animal
skin.
I was like, how did it how are they
going to create the fabric, you know?
So, I kind of gave it up. Not that
it would know, but I just wanted to give
it a little push.
Stretched animal skin, he gets up on it
and when he jumps, it breaks and falls
apart.
And then I tried it again because when
it fell apart, it broke upwards, but it
didn't work. It still gave me the upward
motion. Watch.
Look, it nothing breaks up like that.
Should break down.
I just joined. Where are the prompts?
I'm going over the prompts right now.
Going over the prompts right here live.
Um
the actual prompts
copy and paste prompts are in my Discord
group, but that's not open freely. It's
it's in my behind the plate wall of my
course, which is
uh 25 bucks for the course and you can
get 15% off. The link is in my bio.
Here is my um
here is my group. This is where I put we
have prompts discussion.
People helping each other out with their
prompts.
We also have a whole channel where I
have my
some of the lives that I did. Where is
it? Creator links? No, no. Live workshop
notes.
I have prompts right here. See, every
video has a prompt. I got to update this
still.
I haven't updated it in in about a week
or so.
Maybe a little longer.
If I feel like a video is worth sharing
in there, I do it, but if it's just
normal stuff that everybody in there is
used to, I don't put the prompts in
there cuz most people in there now been
has been through the course.
There's almost I think 600 plus people
now in there.
Let Let just double check. So, when I
say it, I don't always second-guess
myself how many people are in there.
589. So, it's 11 shy from 600. So, close
to 600.
But, if you want to know any prompts,
I'll tell you right here.
All this stuff I share you for free in
my daily lives. You just got to catch me
when I'm on lives.
And uh
but I also have an option that's
everything packaged up for you. And then
I'll give you the monthly
um the access to the Discord group,
which is
which is it's a one-time once you pay
for the course, you're in that you're in
that resource. So,
I call it a monthly resource, but you
don't pay monthly. It's just once you're
in there, it's an ongoing resource, I
should say.
Is that Facebook? Huh?
I don't want anything I'm not I'm not on
Facebook for these lives, no.
Oh, so we have 3,500 likes. Thank you,
guys. Thanks whoever keeps going for me.
I appreciate that. So, let's keep going.
Let's keep going here looking at some of
the prompts here cuz I want to show you
guys some prompts that you can do
yourself.
This is something Let's see. The
This is not the ring camera one as uh AI
Skits was asking me, but this is
something similar. So, watch these.
These are security camera footage at
night.
So, you see that? I'll I'll read it how
how I made that video. Oh, the group.
Now, the group is on an app called
Discord.
The group is on Discord. And like I
said, the only way that you can access
it is by going to my link in bio. And
then you see how the first link is the
course.
Once you get the course, it's you get uh
s-
you get a a access to the group.
Once you join it, you're going to have
access to the group. So, you got a
step-by-step instruction on how to use
this AI, access to the DJI Discord
community. You also have access to the
VO3 prompt optimizer GPT bot, which is a
bot that creates like commercial and
more complex things that you want to
make.
You also have a text-to-video prompt
template for VO3. This is a I'm going to
teach you here how to create the prompts
yourself without relying on chat GPT
right from your head, right from your
own creativity.
And it's a great tool to know it because
one, you're not relying on bots, and
two, you can express your ideas, your
emotion, your humor,
your your product
pretty much any way that you want, as
long as you know how to prompt it.
Okay? That's why I like teaching people
how to write the prompts instead of
relying on the JSON bot.
So, this is what we're doing here today.
So, this is the infrared camera, and all
you have to do
is say this.
Night hunting infrared camera.
A chihuahua sleeping on the grass in a
savanna
is approached by a lion.
Uh the lion growls and picks the
sleeping chihuahua with her mouth and
walks away.
I don't know why I thought of this. I
just remember when like lionesses pick
up their babies.
That's how they carry them.
And then here's another one.
Kid's okay, guys. He's okay. He didn't
pick him up with his mouth.
Yes, AI doesn't understand humor and or
sarcasm. It's great to know how to do
it. Yeah, your videos have a lot of
that. Your videos have a lot of sarcasm
and
I know that you know how to prompt it
well cuz you got great videos, good
great results. I I don't always like
interact with everything cuz I I just
scroll through videos fast. But I do see
your videos, you guys that you guys
share in the group. So, this is the part
where if you go in here into the group,
and there's a part called a section a
channel called
uh
creator links.
And these are the links that people
share when they want to share their
TikTok videos or whatever they're
making. You can share right here. And I
do check each one of them out.
This one was just shared. I haven't
watched this one yet, so I'm not going
to play it on the live. I like I like I
don't like when people post things that
have profanity in the group, so I
discourage you from doing that. And
sometimes I don't play these on live cuz
I haven't tested it out myself yet. I
don't know what it's going to say.
All right. So, let's go back here
uh to this prompt, okay?
I've been trying to get to the next
level. This is it. You follow You found
me.
You know who's at the next level? This
guy right here, look.
You should You should like learn from
him. Follow him.
Let me see if I can Where is he at?
I can't even I can't even find him. How
do you tag somebody on this?
Oh, anyway, show yourself, BK.
And also AI Skits is also at the next
level.
They are at They are at the next level.
Do you know how to monetize this?
You can make ads on TikTok Shop. You can
sell it as a product to market other
products.
Uh I have people DMing me all the time
on TikTok asking me to make uh videos
for their service, for their just like
an AI skit for their roofing company,
for the plumbing company, for the junk
removal company. Like people will find
you and ask you to make
even if you're not making money off the
platform itself,
because you have you have to have 10,000
followers and videos over a minute.
This is just a tool that you can use in
the real world
and your local businesses. A lot of
people are trying to communicate a
vision. They're trying to market a
service. They're trying to promote a
product.
Um
they're trying to promote an event, and
you can use AI for that. You guys don't
be limited to this this humor like all
this stuff that you see on social media
that's not adding any value to anything.
Like a lot of my stuff
is just things that yeah, they're
they're trendy and all that. What I
don't know it it's a
in my market. My market is teaching you
how to use this tool. So in my market it
helps my cause
to make a video like this that gets 3
million views.
Some of you are asking That's 3 million
eyeballs that I get
to look at my profile
and see what I offer.
And the course came after this this blew
up by the way. The course came after cuz
people wanted to they were the enemy for
like one on ones. I did a bunch of one
on one calls with people. But I could
only do like three or four a day of
those and my my time, you know, 4 hours
went by and I helped four people. I
rather just put everything that I was
teaching in those one hour
calls
that I charge a lot for cuz it's one
hour of my time
and put that into a package deal where
it's like 25 bucks and you can get
everything. So So that is a channel that
I found through making these videos. But
again,
um
you can you can make good money with
these if you know exactly where to look.
So I don't know what your market is. I
don't know what your talents are. I
don't know what your skills are. I don't
know how your time is structured like.
So when you ask a question like that, I
can't give you a specific answer cuz it
depends on you.
So that was a long-winded answer for
you.
But
going back to these prompts. Here's
more. Let's see what this one does.
There's a lion goes in
smells the dog
roars, they both get up
and they salute the
and they salute the camera.
All right. So I made I made I made quite
a few of these.
All these I make on my lives guys by the
way.
I make them on my lives and then this
live here I'm showing you what's already
been made. If you If you guys want we
can do some prompting from scratch.
Um but I'm not going to get to that
until we have a bigger room in here. So
if people are interested, they they to
jump in.
We can burn some of my credits up.
This was when the whole
uh
fruit cutting ones were popular. I don't
know if they still are.
But I'll play it for you here.
And I'll read the prompt.
So, cereal glass fruit hyperrealistic
being sliced slow motion ASMR style by a
fancy medieval
add crisp knife sound, pops, and drips.
So, this is how you can create this on
Google Flow.
This is what I'm using. If you're just
joining me, or if you don't know
where I'm putting these prompts. A lot
of people when I post my videos and I
give you the prompts, they're like,
"Where do I put it
Where do I put these prompts? ChatGPT?"
I'm like, "No, no, you have to go in
and put it into Google Flow, and that's
accessible through a Google AI Pro
subscription."
And all the links that you need for
these are in my bio. If you go here on
the way to the bottom, see AI tools.
Google AI Pro
V03.
And this is not an affiliate. They don't
have an affiliate for this. This is just
for you to easily access it if you want
if you want to.
Okay. So,
let me go show you some
real-life examples on how you can use
this.
It's not V0 and Gemini.
You can use it in Gemini. V0 is
accessible through Gemini or Google
Flow.
But if you have
if you have um uh Google AI Pro
subscription you're leaving
prompts on the table by not using Google
Flow. Cuz Google Flow gives you
to um 50 V03 fast prompts a month.
You can use Gemini, but you're limited
to three a day, right?
It was not and no sound.
Yeah, try try Flow. If you have If you
have access to Am I right to say you
guys that know help me out cuz I I don't
know for sure.
V um Gemini
doesn't allow you to create VO3 videos
unless you have the paid plan, right?
I don't know if they opened it up to be
like, oh, now you can make like one a
day, whatever. I'm not sure cuz I
haven't checked it. But
Flow is way better, it's true. Yeah, so
this is what I'm trying to get with
this.
If you have Gemini
and you're making VO3 videos
and you have a paid plan you're leaving
prompts on the table. Which is also
money on the table by not using Flow.
Flow is way better.
It has better um
response with with the prompts.
It gives you better results.
And just give me 1 second, folks. Give
me 1 second.
Yes, no problem, no problem. So here we
have more Let's Let's look at some stuff
that you can All my real life examples
of like things that I did for businesses
are in Well, this is one that I did.
Are in another account. So this is one
that I did for somebody on TikTok that
asked me to make a video for their gator
neck gator um brand.
So I did I did one, but I didn't really
look I didn't really like the way it
looked. Let me play it for you. When the
Texas sun hits like a mic See how See
how it glitched and his mouth came
through?
And also I didn't like the look. It was
nothing was really like eye-catching. It
was very bland. So I added the American
flag. I added a cowboy hat. Just give it
some more characteristics to the video.
Some more, you know. Thank you for the
gifts, The Godfather. I appreciate it.
I feel like a grandpa. Hey Dana, how's
it going, man?
Hey, I didn't know about this about um
two two months ago either, so
I'm in video production, but I felt like
a grandpa not knowing this stuff until I
learned it and I loved it. All right, so
here's another video from
Here's the second video from this guy.
He's on here on TikTok. His account's
called Flex Form. He sells neck neck
gaiters. So, he reached out to me in the
early days of when I started doing this.
See, June 19th.
And he asked me if I could make a video
for his brand. So, then after that, I
took on a bunch of new people. I was
making videos for them. I think I was
charging like
$60 per video.
I don't know how much. 60?
Feel like it was 60 or 80, I forget.
Maybe I upped it to 80. And then
eventually I stopped answering them
cuz it wasn't it was just too much time
and it was too much back and forth. So,
here's one
that was a successful video that I
created. And in 8 seconds I made 60
bucks.
When the Texas sun hits like a microwave
on high, you need gear that can handle
the heat. Same grit, different day. Flex
Form, baby. When the Texas sun So, you
see how you have a different angle? I
want to show you how to do that in a
second.
What app can I use to create an animated
cartoon and keep the same one every
video I create? So, you got to start
Michelle. You got to start with
an image, okay? If you're going to use
Google Flow, Google VEO3, this is what I
teach here. This is what I'm used to.
This is what I'm expert at.
Um
or at least I have a lot of experience.
I don't know about expert.
But, if you're going to use this
platform, which is Google Google Flow,
it makes VEO3 videos. V E O 3. That's
the engine behind it. It's the It's the
It's the model.
Um
over here to create consistent
characters, you're going to need to use
the frames to video option.
And let me see one thing. 1 second.
Let me see 1 second. One thing here.
Let me make sure that this doesn't have
any customer images in here.
>> All right, I'm just cleaning out some of
the images here that I have
from other brands.
All right, so let's get back here. So,
all right.
So, once you go in here into the prompt
box inside of Google VO3,
I'm looking to see who all who's all in
here.
Make sure I'm not missing any. Saying
hello to some of our subscribers.
Some of our subscription members here on
on TikTok.
So, once you go in the prompt box, we
have frames to video. This is where you
would click
and then add your first frame. So,
uh
So, here. This is a consistent character
that I was making a skit of. So, here we
are. First picture,
second picture,
third picture, all right?
Now, if you want to create an animated
character that you have yourself, like
you have already a picture of him. Let's
say it's something like a Funko Pop or
like it looks, you know, it's not
generated by AI. It's a real-life
character or something that you already
have pre-made.
You got to take that character into a
photo
AI, like ChatGPT or or Midjourney or
what else?
Um
Hixfield.
There's a bunch of AIs that are just
images. Like they're really good at
making images and consistent characters.
Uploading that character there and then
creating consistent first frames of your
videos. And then that's the second step
is now you bringing you bringing your
frames to Google Flow and you upload
your frames. So, here I have Let me get
out of the way so you can see. I have
one,
two, and three, four
of the same character. So, once you load
it, that's going to be the first frame
of your video. So, you can just type in
I just saw like something come up on my
screen.
Oh, it was a nice gift. Thank you, the
Godfather. Appreciate it. Heart it out.
That with that my goal has already been
reached. I think they're going to push
it up automatically. So, if you see that
goal move up, it's because automatically
it goes up.
Holy crap, he sent me a galaxy. That's
my first one.
Is that true? Let's see. Why can't I see
it? I want to get the whole the full the
full uh
the full effect. Let me pull it up on my
phone, so I have it. I think I'll see
the replay. I'll go back and see the
replay once I end my live. I really
appreciate that, sir.
All right, so
That's crazy. Appreciate you. Thank you.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you.
Uh where were where were we with this
thing? I love I love to share this
stuff, whether it's uh whether it's here
on TikTok or in real life, I talk to
people about stuff and it's sometimes it
just leads to AI.
So, I want to read you this prompt that
I made for to create the same video that
I Oh, oh. I know where I was going. I
forget. Somebody asked me about the
consistent character. So, if you're
still here, this is how you make them.
Once you have the first frame, I'm going
to show you what to do with it cuz I
made a whole story about it.
On my last on my two lives ago, we did a
whole consistent character workshop.
Michelle, okay, you're still here. Okay,
this is a whole lesson that I did a
consistent character workshop.
Uh it was like our lives that we did
here.
So, here's the consistent character,
okay?
Let me play you this first frame.
Remember, these are pictures I I create
this these pictures here were made using
an a AI image creator. You can use
Gemini, you can use ChatGPT, you can use
Midjourney, but the every first frame
was created using that. So, I I
emphasized that enough. Now you Now you
know how I how I created this this look
right here. So, once I uploaded the
first frame, so frames to video, I click
plus.
I uploaded the first frame, which was
that.
Right here. See? I loaded this up. So,
now it's like, all right, what do you
want me to do with this, sir? So, then I
went ahead and said, character looks at
the camera. This is a prompt. This is
all you have to say. Character looks at
the camera and says, okay guys, I've
been walking for 15 miles and haven't
seen a soul. I'm walking towards what I
think is a lake. We shall see. So, here
we go. Let's play it.
Okay guys, I've been walking for 15
miles and haven't seen a soul, and I'm
walking towards what I think is a lake.
We shall see.
Oh, you use
What's going on here, Tik Tok? What do
you want from me? There seems to be a
problem with the live. Okay.
You guys see any problems on your side?
Anything happening?
Man, I really appreciate the Godfather
sending me all those gifts. I don't know
if he's still here, but
that was
I'm not usually a live gift person. You
know what I mean? Like, I don't usually
get gifts cuz I'm not I don't I don't do
battles or anything like that. I just
come in here and give you guys the info.
Lag for me, but I think it was just me.
No, I think it's a lag for you. I mean,
it's I think it's a lag. So, it says, it
seems like there are problems with your
live. I'm just trying to create a
consistent character here for you guys,
and this thing keeps messing me up.
Uh try to improve your live. Reduce the
bit rate. Okay. Let me take a screenshot
of this so I can do this later cuz I'm
not doing this right now.
If there I keep having this problem, I'm
going to just uh end it and then come
back on.
But, I took a screenshot of took a
picture of the this the tips that
they're giving me.
Don't show this to me again.
Hide.
All right, anyway.
Um great. You have You have um You have
Gemini. So, I'll show you how to use
this I use Gemini for this, too. There's
a built-in way that you can create these
videos here in Gemini.
And
Yeah, so after the live, don't don't do
this now, but after the live, go to my
go to my Tik Tok cuz I'm going to show
you to you now.
And watch this video right here.
Okay. Okay, folks. Game changer feature.
You can now preview the scene in Google
VO. So this video right here, watch that
video.
>> Okay, folks. It's a tutorial on how to
do
what I'm about to show you how to do,
but it's like a brief tutorial. It's
like a minute long.
So I'm going to show you how to do this
here now step-by-step. So let's go back
where I was. That was this day. Yeah. So
I'll play this prompt for you so you can
see how it worked out. I think I did it
already, but I'll try it again cuz I
forget if I did it or not.
Okay, guys. I've been walking for 15
miles and haven't seen a soul, and I'm
walking towards what I think is a lake.
We shall see. All right, so that's that.
And then the second frame
to to continue the story, character
looks at the camera and says, "Okay,
here I am now." I'll play instead of
reading it. So I essentially just said
character says, and then I typed what
he's going to say.
Okay, I'm here now and
yep.
It was a mirage, a freaking optical
illusion.
So you see that shot right here?
That is a it's called a cut-to shot. So
I after I wrote, "Okay, I'm here now.
Yeah, it was a mirage, an optical
illusion."
I typed in the prompt, "Cut to aerial
shot of desert." So this is how you can
show your character's world inside your
your your 8-second video cuz remember
these these videos are limited to 8
seconds.
Once you uploaded that first frame,
which is this one right here,
the GPT knows the world that he lives
in. And by the way, there is an update
coming.
Uh not to flow, but it's it's not an
update. I shouldn't say update. It's a
different It's part of It's part of the
Google DeepMind
uh library of of AIs.
I forget what it's called, but it's
going to be a game engine where it's
it's it generates a world I It uses I'm
pretty sure it uses the same technology
that this is using to do something like
this. You see that?
When I said cut to aerial shot of the
desert, no captions, it created the same
environment that he's in.
See those mountains in the back, the red
rocks with the flat tops?
Here they are. Look, red rocks, the flat
tops.
So, I think this is borrowing from the
other technology that Google DeepMind is
is coming out with. It's essentially
going to be a gaming engine where people
going to be able to write a prompt, and
then your world will exist, and you can
walk in it like a game. So, anything
that you put in your world, it's going
to generate frame by frame in real time.
So, it's pretty much going to be the end
of
the end of gaming developers having to
do it manually, cuz I think they're
going to be able to do this now using
AI. It's going to be amazing. I forget
what it's called, but it's a it's a
Google product. And it's a it's a 3D
virtual world using AI.
So, then the third scene, folks, is this
one here.
Hey, buddy.
>> Same Same character. Are you real?
Do you know where I can find some water?
Bro, are you serious?
So, he's gatekeeping.
I just heard something outside, so I'll
just try to listen. He's gatekeeping the
water information. So, for Michelle, let
me show you how to do this um
Let me show you how to create these
inside of
Flow, these images. Now, Gemini and Flow
are joined together.
Now,
I might have to look at my
tutorial to remind myself
how to get there. Oh, I know. I
remember. All right. So, once you're in
a Google Flow window, right, create with
Flow. I'm going to start from scratch.
Create with Flow. Once you're here,
hit create with Flow. I didn't get that.
Could you try again? All right. All
right, Siri. Relax. I wasn't talking to
you.
All right. Once you go with Flow, we're
going to going to go new project.
And right here, frames to video,
click that, click plus. Generate image.
You see this? Is this what you using
before? Maybe you already know what you
Oh, I'm talking about.
But this is where you're going to
generate that image. Look, generate
image. And this is where you're going to
create your consistent character. This
does not take any credits away from you.
Um these image generation, okay?
So it does not take any credit away from
you. It only takes a credit away once
you
create your video. Right now, this is a
text to image prompt. And by the way, if
you're here on TikTok and you want to
see this full screen, there's a little
square somewhere that you can click if
you haven't discovered that already.
It'll take It'll take you uh from
vertical to sideways so you can see it
better.
All right. So here, text to image. Let's
create a a character here, all right?
Let's say
What if I just use Gemini to prompt this
as a nice character? I don't feel like
tapping. Hold on.
Let's go.
Let's use AI to make us an AI character.
Let's go to Gemini. Oh, thanks. And say
uh create a
text prompt
for a
I don't know. For a character
that I can use
in my story.
Describe the
character look,
the setting,
and the feel
of the shot.
And then I can even say like
make it
fantasy related.
Uh
All right, let's see. Let's see. I never
did this before. I just had an idea to
see if it would even work.
Go to the uh uh it wants more it wants
my information. Please tell me a little
more about the kind of character you
imagine. For example, what's the role in
the story? Hero.
Uh
I'm just going to say
a cute character
for
younger audiences.
Jimmy, thank you. I appreciate that.
Some people don't appreciate that I'm
showing you this
for different reasons. All right, so
here, this is what um I'm going way
deeper than I don't know what I have to
I just didn't feel like thinking about a
character, okay? Look, a tiny fluffy
creature with oversized sparkling eyes
that changes color with its mood.
All right, let's just let's just get get
copy this, okay? Copy this over. Let's
go to the image prompt.
Where Where am I at? Right here. Let's
put that in. I don't even know if it's
going to work. This is the first time
I've done this. I just didn't feel like
typing.
So, let's do a text to image.
All right, it's going to create four
different images for us. I'm excited. I
don't even I don't even know what it's
going to look like at all.
Ah, look at that, folks. Look how cute
this is.
I I don't like the different color eyes,
but it's I think it happened because we
said something about his eyes changes
colors
with the mood, so it was different
colors.
This is Google Flow, my friend. This is
Jimmy. It's called Google Flow.
So then, uh Michelle, look, this is the
character, right?
Let me say this now.
Same character
in the same
setting
but a close-up shot.
You can create your own cartoon series
right here. Same character in the same
setting but a close-up shot. Let's see
if it works.
Again, I haven't tried this before.
I'm just I do this lives and half the
time I don't know what I'm doing.
I just learn along with you.
Everything I learn, I learn from DJI.
He's a great teacher. Oh, I appreciate
that. Thank you.
Oh, no, look. It didn't work. You have
to I know I know I know what I did
wrong.
It doesn't know what the same character
looks like. This is not ChatGPT. Look,
it gave me something else.
Yeah, so when I said same character,
it's not ChatGPT. ChatGPT will give you
the same character, but not Gemini.
Gemini is a little slower.
So, what do I want to do here?
Let me think, folks. Let me think.
I might have to just put in the whole
prompt again, like this.
Let me get the prompt.
And then just just change what I want to
see change. So, a tiny fluffy creature
with oversized sparkling eyes that
change color with his mood, has two
small leafy antennas.
Setting,
the ground is covered blah blah blah,
gentle la la.
The scene is captured from a low angle.
Oh, this is where you change the scene
now. This is what I want.
From a low angle,
close-up shot.
I'm making this more complicated than it
has to be just because I just cheated on
the prompt, but you can type in your own
prompts to make it simple. Emphasize the
character's small size. I don't need all
this.
Uh
They can leave the colors. Let's see if
it works. If not, do this in ChatGPT.
I don't know about um So, when I did my
Bigfoot one that I just showed you,
I just kept saying Bigfoot Bigfoot
Bigfoot and it kept giving me the same
character look.
So, it knows how to do Bigfoot, but when
it comes to creatures that never existed
inside of the the world,
All All here's here's the other one that
we just made, right?
It's not a close-up shot though. So,
this is the first batch.
And then this is the second one that we
just did right now.
It's the same character, right? It gives
us different
So, that one is a cool one.
I don't see cuz they give us different
versions of them of it. So, what one
here, I like that. And then
I like that one. All right, so let's
let's go ahead and So, what do you do
with these, right? So, next time you
want another image, you can just paste
the same prompt and right here feel the
shot. You can say shot from behind, shot
from the side, um super close-up shot.
Just change it up. It It's free to
create these anyway. Like you're not
burning credits.
So,
can you do a two image and animate
between them? So, now we're going to
animate them, okay? So, let's go ahead
and find the one that we like first. I
think I think this one's nice and clean
right here. This or this.
You can even reuse it. Like
yeah, reuse it as a frame. Why not? So,
let's go ahead You can save these by the
way. Right click and save it to your
computer. So, if you lose it, you know
where it is.
Uh if you like lost this session right
here, it's you still have it. So, let's
go ahead and animate this character. So,
we're going to do use this image. You
see where it says right here? Oh, right
here.
Use this character.
We're going to click that. Use this
image, I mean.
So, now it loaded that as the first
frame.
All right, I uploaded that as the first
frame. So, here we're going to write
character cuz look, every time I teach
this about the prompts. And I keep
saying this all my people that have been
here that have my class and my course
and are in the Discord group,
they're probably tired of hearing it.
But every time you write a prompt,
you're going to need five things. You're
going to need a character, a setting, a
shot composition. Shot composition is
like medium close-up, wide shot, aerial
shot,
um
uh wide extra wide shot, things like
that. Like side shot. So, that's a
composition. And then the fourth thing
is an action in the dialogue. When you
have a photo, you already have the
character description locked in. The
character is that right there, acorn
little green thing. The setting is
already there. It's a mystical magical
world, fantasy-like, right? The
character is in the setting there.
And the shot composition is there. That
is a wide shot. It shows the full body,
so that's a wide shot. So, you don't
have to write the those three things.
So, now you only have two more things
remaining. The two more things remaining
are what? Your action and your dialogue.
So, here, let's describe the action.
Character
Let me see. Let me see the picture
bigger so I can imagine something that
it does.
I forgot what it looks like now.
What is What is it surrounding it? Okay,
so
what is it doing? He's going to What is
he going to do? He's going to walk
across the river. All right, let's do
that. Character
um walks
across
the river.
And then I'm going to put mystical
music.
How do you spell mystical? I I miss I
purposely misspelled that so I can have
AI help me. Mystical
music
in the background.
I'm going to say playful. I don't want
it to be like
mystical playful music in the
background. Let's keep it simple. Let's
see if that works. Again, I've never
made this one before. I have no idea if
it's going to work.
But this is what we do here. All right,
character walks across the river
mystical playful music in the
background.
Let's send it. So, now, Michelle, you're
going to be able to
lock it in, right? First frame.
And then you're going to be able to have
the character
do what you said.
Right here. Let me move myself out of
this out of the way.
And let's hit send right here. Make sure
that this is on VO3 fast, okay?
Anything else you don't want. It's VO3
fast is what we want. It only takes 20
credits.
So, frames to video, we sent that.
Now, if we go back to generate image,
while that's making, let's go back. So,
this is how you go back to that again.
You go to plus, you go to generate
image.
Because the only one that's loaded in
here, it's the one that you clicked use
this image. Remember when you clicked
use this image?
That's the only one that's loaded there.
So, if you go to generate image,
Michelle, you're going to go ahead and
find another image that you like
to start with.
So, here it can be that he's across the
river. So, this is the one that before
he crossed it,
right? And now he's across the river
right here. The river See, he's on the
left. He's on the left here of the
river.
And then here he's on the right.
Let me find one that where he doesn't
have the speckles.
Ah, is there one no one with the
speckles?
Ah.
Yeah, this is the one I liked cuz it's
on the right.
But,
it's all right. It can be a different
angle. It's all right. So, let's use
this one as our as our second frame,
okay?
And then also, you can take this.
Let's let's let's take a screenshot of
this. You can save it as well.
I'm going to use ChatGPT for the next
step here. Well, let's let's go ahead
and and and see how that video plays out
first. I want to do a second angle, but
like a close-up angle of him.
And I don't think Gemini is going to
help me with it.
So, I'm going to use Gemini to help me
with it.
So, we're going to do use this image,
okay?
That's our second image right here. Use
this image. So, it's loaded. It's ready
to go. Let's watch this and see how it
worked out, okay guys?
If you can help me to please get our
like a live to 10,000 likes, the people
that are in here, teamwork.
Teamwork, we have 6,000 likes right now.
The more taps, the more people come in.
So, let's go ahead and play this.
Hopefully it works. I'm not sure. I
never used animation like this before.
Oh, he walks forward, okay.
Oh, the river is over here.
That's cool.
They listen to the music.
Are you going to have the character
talk? Yeah, we can.
We can try to make them talk next time
here.
I love this. I can play it all over
again.
All right, the thing about me putting
music is this. The next scene, if you
want to stitch them together, most
likely that that song will not keep
going.
So, uh you kind of shoot shoot yourself
in the foot by doing music. Uh but I
have an idea, actually. Let me Let me
We're going to abandon this for right
now, the first frame. I think I can
continue this with the music
with VO2.
It's the first time ever I'm going to
use VO2 on a live.
Okay, let's try it. VO2 that There's no
I don't even know if it's going to work.
Let's see. Look, add to scene.
Add to scene. So, we're going to
continue it. We're going to continue it
from where where he left off. And then
right here we're going to click click
plus, and we're going to extend it. You
see where it says extend?
What should happen next?
You can't make them talk on this one.
So, maybe we'll make them talk the next
time. But here, this is going to use
VO2.
Well, let's leave it VO3 fast so you can
see what happens. So, what happens next?
I'm going to say character
keeps walking
and
picks up
a
What is that called? A a mushroom
from the ground.
I think I'm going to keep it simple.
Yeah, you can add music in CapCut. I
just wanted to make the like the whole,
you know, vibe better. Character keeps
walking and picks up a mushroom from the
ground.
Um
And just in case I I more time, cuz it's
8 seconds, right? I'm going to see him
looks at it.
You got to take small
small looks like berries.
Oh, yeah. I know. I was talking about
the ones in the behind it, the glowing
things.
All right. So, character keeps walking
and picks up mushroom from the ground
and looks at it.
It's kind of boring, but look look what
happens when you try to extend it and
send it with the VO2 VO3 fast.
This feature doesn't support a VO3 fast.
Switch to VO2 fast. Let's switch it to
VO2.
Again, I don't I don't use VO2 for
anything, but I just thought I had an
idea to try to use that here. VO2 is
lower quality. Let's Let's put it to the
test.
Just If it doesn't work, just scratch
everything that just happened from this
moment on.
Let's send it in see if VO2 is good for
anything.
All right. So, all that's going there.
Um
Let's see if we can cover some ground
here.
Yeah, this we already went through this,
right?
I'm going to close that.
Yeah, so these videos are
They're so much fun. I can make these
all day. And this is what I pretty much
what I do.
Let's go back here now.
All right. So, we have 50 plus people in
the room finally, and that's thanks to
your tapping on that screen. So, if you
can get to 10,000, that would be
awesome, folks. See, we had 35 when we
first asked for that, and now we have
50.
I'm telling you that they did enough to
know that the more you tap,
it's like every 10 taps is a different
person that gets served these videos.
All right. Let's see how VO Has anyone
used VO2 before? I'm curious to know.
Let's play this. The first 8 seconds is
VO3, and then the last 8 seconds is VO2.
And also keep keep note Make sure that
Let's see if the music keeps going or
not.
Okay? As soon as that cursor crosses
over,
All right, so no music.
But it's pretty good.
Yeah, it's it's it wasn't enough
instructions, guys.
I made it do too little. So it it
started doing some AI glitch. So like it
picked up the mushroom, put it back.
So it's 8 seconds, right? It's an option
for you that you can use. There's no
audio, but look.
Yeah, no audio at all.
It added ears, really? Let me see.
I didn't even notice it.
Oh, yeah. Well, maybe the ears were
hiding.
Maybe the ears were hiding, who knows?
All right, hold on.
I got to I got to go in this chat and
type in here
sometimes cuz TikTok will tell me that
I'm not being active.
Yeah, I don't know about that. It's
it's it's cool, but you can see the
quality change a little bit. You see how
nice and sharp I I don't know if you
guys see this in in over the the the
stream, but in real life this is like
more fuzzy.
But nevertheless, hey, it's an option.
It's only 10 credits, too, instead of
20.
It did add ears, but maybe the ears were
always there behind it.
All right, anyway, so let's scrap that
one. So let's go ahead and right here
where it says um
arrange, just delete it right here.
Click the minus.
And it's gone.
And then we hit done.
Now,
let's do a frames to video again. Let's
go back to our original plan. This is
why I like testing things out. Click
plus.
Generate image. Oh, it's already there.
I forgot. We already loaded it.
Cancel.
We already loaded that one. Here it is.
All right, so he's in the middle of the
river here.
Oh, he's he's This is the other one.
Okay, I got it. So now we're going to do
this. This is a whole new prompt.
It's a whole new prompt. So we go back
to VO3 fast. Let's make him talk now.
Character
His stick turned into a mushroom. It
did? I didn't even notice all that.
So, character
uh looks
at uh
Let's see what kind of voice it gives it
gives it, you know.
Camera
and says he's going to be like
I I wish a voice I can control it, but
I'm not even going to try cuz it doesn't
work when you try to control it.
Hey there, friends. Hey there, friends.
I need some water.
Hey there, friends.
Will you help me? It's going to be like
a little Dora.
A little Dora the Explorer kind of kind
of a vibe on this. Hey there, friends.
Will you help me
get
to
the troll bridge?
I need to find a
magic
flower.
Is that too much? Too long? Let's see.
You got to count in your head. I will
say this. You got to read it out loud
and count in your head how long is it
going to take to say this cuz it's 8
seconds limited, okay? Hey friends, will
you help me get to the troll bridge?
I need to find a magic flower.
Did he pay the troll toll?
So, I need I need two more seconds of
something quick to
to heal
my friend.
Might be too long.
Hey there, friends. Will you help me get
to the troll bridge? I need to find a
magic flower to heal my friend.
I'm not going to say that. I'm going to
say
my friend is sick.
All right, let's see if that works.
Go ahead and send it. So, the first
frame is right here.
Uh fast frames the video, send it.
This is a way, by the way, that you can
add the videos up all together inside of
the same timeline instead of having to
individually create them, cuz I can
individually create them out out here
like this.
Like one.
And then go ahead and do like one. And
then like again the two.
And this is how they're created in here.
But if you want to use them in the
timeline kind of situation, you can
create them in in this add to scene
where
you can export the whole entire thing
and that therefore it makes it longer
than 8 seconds. Cuz a lot of people
like, "How do I make it longer than 8
seconds?" Well, this is how.
Now, the problem with the consistent
character um
is that you have to keep generating
images for every scene that you want to
see that character in. And as we just
saw with Gemini,
it didn't listen to my request. So, I'm
going to try it one more time with
Gemini.
While that's loading, let's go ahead and
try to load our next frame, okay?
Maybe maybe it's going to get there
quick. Hold on.
I thought YouTube demonetized this type
of content.
I don't think they did. It's It's You
got to read their I I saw a video that
somebody was saying that it's people
just took it under a different light. It
was It wasn't that It wasn't what the
policy said at all.
Ah, you know what? Look, I just got an
error message that says, um you can't
generate the voice because it's a minor.
Well, that doesn't make any sense. It
added a nose to him.
Oh, no.
I just got a pop-up that said you can't
generate images for a minor. So, I think
I know what happens here.
It thinks this is like a kid. You can
only make minors or people of all ages,
let's say, talk when it's a text prompt,
when it's a complete text prompt like
this.
You can make like the babies talk and
people of all ages, right?
But when you upload an image,
it thinks this is like a minor.
Or it knows that it's like made for kids
or something and it didn't want to give
me the audio. I just got a pop-up that
said your audio was not generated.
Too bad. It would have been cool.
It did add a nose to it, though. I don't
like that.
That would have been perfect, except the
nose. And then, of course, if it had
audio.
Trying to think how do you bypass this?
I think I know how. Hold on.
Let me go ahead and copy this.
I'm going to try to Gemini it.
Gemini is kind of slower.
Gemini won't catch that.
So, here we're going to do tools.
No, what are we going to do here? Let's
see. Hold on 1 second.
I'm going to I'm going to try to make
that scene on Gemini.
All right, here I am in Gemini, okay?
I'm going to add a photo.
Ah, I don't have that photo saved.
Well,
I have to save it then, huh?
Where was that photo at, guys?
At this point, we're just going to keep
trying this cuz I want to make make it
work. If it If it doesn't work on
Gemini, then
I don't know. Maybe maybe the character
has to look a little older. I'm not sure
I sent the AI key key creature. I don't
know why they think it's a it's a
person.
So, I have to go back and save that
image, folks, to my computer. So,
I got to open this up.
I got to go back here, generate image,
right? Go back to the source.
Uh, which one is the image right here,
right? So, I got to right click and
save.
I'm going to save this image to my
computer cuz Gemini doesn't know
about this this dashboard right here.
Make sense?
So, I got to save it.
And then, we're going to go to Gemini.
Add.
There it is. So, I added the photo.
Ah,
I did it it didn't copy for some reason.
Let's go copy the prompt.
Copy the prompt. Where is it at? Cancel.
Here, character looks at the camera and
says,
I got to put that seed back on there.
Here, Gemini.
Character looks at the camera and says,
"Hey there, blah blah." Okay.
All right, let's send that.
All right, so while that's going,
let's see. Let's see. I'm going to leave
this live here to see if the message
will come up. Cuz I've gotten away with
doing some stuff that flow couldn't do
it. Said that the policy was broken or
something.
Yeah, this is this right here is Gemini,
but I'm using Google Flow for most of my
this this is Google Flow. It's the same
thing pretty much. It Gemini does videos
as well, but it uses the same
technology that is Google Flow's using.
It's just a different way to access
that.
video capability.
Yeah, so anyway, um
the YouTube did not demonetize AI stuff.
You got to read into look into that a
little further cuz people panicked and
started putting that out there.
But it
I don't know exactly what it was
demonetized about AI, but it wasn't it
wasn't making videos like this cuz
obviously things like this take
creativity.
Did it make audio?
No audio. So it just didn't give me the
Okay.
So it didn't give me the
the error message, but it still made no
audio.
There's the stupid captions. That always
happens.
Yeah, too bad with this character, but
there's other ones that you can make.
Maybe something older.
Let's try to do um
I'm what I'm showing you this how to
make these prompts with these
animations or or other things, it's the
same concept. So I'm going to keep
I'm going to keep going with something
like this.
Trying to animate it. So let me go back
and see if I can find that prompt again.
And I'm just going to modify it.
I'm going to modify it to make it look
older.
See if it works.
So we went here and um
Here, character.
I'm just going to say make the character
look older.
About
25. I don't know. Give it an age.
Didn't they had a bug that would not
generate voices?
No, this is not a bug though. This is a
problem with the It thinks the character
is young. It thinks it's a kid. It does
not generate audio for kids if you have
an image with it.
It will only do it if it's a complete
text prompt.
A young woman with a wild cascade of
Okay, let's I don't even want to read
it. Let's just Let's be surprised. Let's
be surprised.
All right. So, we got four generations.
It's going to help us. Thanks for the
gift, Sky Flutter.
Appreciate that.
Uh let's see. Let's see.
Uh it's it's a 2D though. I don't want
that.
I mean, we could use it, right? Why not?
It's fine.
We can do a three this real
ultra-realistic. Let me see. Let me try
on ultra
realistic.
See what that does.
Upload it to 11 labs or CapCut to the
audio. Yeah, but it won't match the lip
the
the lips.
It won't match the the syncing, you know
what I mean?
It only works if you have a um
the audio already there and you can take
it to CapCut I mean to
If the audio is there and you want to
match the same voice throughout cuz the
voice will be different, you can put it
into 11 labs and then 11 labs will
transform that audio into the same voice
for you.
Yeah, it's still not ultra-realistic.
Somewhere in there there's something
about a cartoon. I'm not reading all
this. But somewhere in here it talks
about it being cartoon-like. So,
I like it's the same character though.
Look, she It gave me the entire
I like this one. All right, I'll use
this.
Let's make it talk.
Character What is that? What is that
What is that a wand?
Would you call that a wand? What would
you call that? I want that to glow.
I want to say that character's wand
glows.
I'll CapCut Well, CapCut will add audio
to it and make the lips move.
Staff, that's it. It's a staff.
Character's staff glows.
Character says,
"Welcome
to the magical
land of" What's the name of this place?
Give me a name.
Welcome to the magical land of" Remember
that picture?
It was like a place with trees.
What's the name of the place? Give me a
Give me a cool name for this fantasy
land.
That might not even get read out because
it thinks it's a child.
Wonderland?
That's very generic.
To the magical to the enchanted land of
Wonderland, maybe?
Cuz I don't want to say uh
magical land of I thought that's fine.
I thought magical and and wonderland was
too close, but it's not.
Magical land of Wonderland
where
anything is possible.
Cut to
wide shot
wide shot of
setting
as
character
walks.
Um
I'm just going to say that.
I wanted to change the scene to see if
it will understand um
as character walks.
All right.
Character says, "Welcome to the magical
land of Wonderland where anything's
possible." Cut to wide shot of setting
as character walks. Okay, the setting
meaning like the environment.
VO3 fast, frames to video.
And then if you want to end it with a
certain frame, you can end it with a
certain frame right here by clicking the
second one, but I never really use that.
You can end it in a certain frame if you
had it.
All right, let's let's pray that this
will make it talk.
All right.
I think it will. I don't see why it
wouldn't. I made Oh, you know what? I
made a whole cartoon before with this.
Let me show you Michelle, let me show
you what I made.
I forget that I did something like this
with a consistent character. Watch this
entire
play right here. And I do have the
prompts. This video right here has the
prompts in it. So if you're interested
in learning how the prompts worked,
but watch this. I'm so glad I found you,
and I can't wait to have a family with
you.
We will make a great couple.
Crap, she found me.
She's serious about that child support.
Did you enjoy that? We are unpaid AI
actors. Want to learn how to make these
films? Check the link in bio.
I'm so glad I found you, and I can't
wait to have a
So that was one with the consistent
character. And then this video right
here
shows you the prompts underneath it. I'm
so glad I found you. And that's how I
built that out.
>> to have a family with you.
We will make a great couple.
Crap, she found me.
She's serious about that child support.
Did you enjoy that? We So that video you
just watched, this is how I built it in
the TikTok app
with all the different clips.
Uh
I did that at night in bed. I remember
now. I was just laying there late and I
started making that.
And then I screen recorded.
Let's see if we can find it here. All
right, please say something.
Here we go, folks. Let's watch it.
Welcome to the magical land of
Wonderland, where anything is possible.
Nice.
Nice, this is great.
This is awesome. What do you think?
Let's see that tap on that screen,
folks, if you like this one.
Let me put a poll out there. We'll see
if we like that one or not. Should I
Should I do a second Should I do a
second scene?
My voice is not good doing well today.
Too much lies, big people.
I need some warm tea, not cold water.
All right, if you want to see a second
scene,
put the happy face on. If you want to
see a different scene, different
different topic, different visual,
sad face.
Or if you don't care,
at least pick one and vote. Just so we
can interact. You see that on the
screen, folks? You see that on the
screen?
Try to tap that. See if you like uh
So you can give me some interaction. You
can Tik Tok thinks I'm I'm I'm sleeping
on this live.
I can't believe I got a galaxy on this
live. It's awesome.
Looks like a scene from a game. It does.
Let me play that again. I like that,
man.
Welcome to the magical land of
Wonderland, where anything is possible.
You see the glowing stick the staff?
It's a glowing. See it?
And then look at the Look at the Look at
the floor. It's like illuminated as
she's walking. That's amazing.
All right, so three
against one. All right, so the one
person, I'm sorry, but we're going to
make another one of those. So again, to
access the whole entire library of
images where she was, we got to go back
to plus, generate, and this is all the
images that we generated, okay?
Let's pick a different scene here.
What if I said, let me go back to that
this right here.
Uh all those look pretty similar to me,
guys. Like all these I don't want to
reuse any of these. They all look
similar. Maybe she stops somewhere else.
But I want a complete change.
A young woman with a wild Let me I have
to read this cuz I have to make it
perfect now cuz I wanted the
consistency. A young woman with a wild
cascade of copper hair
interwoven with delicate vines and tiny
luminescents flowers. Her eyes are color
of a twilight sky and they hold the
wisdom.
Oh, wow, I got deep here with this
stuff. Yeah, it sparkles with youthful
mischief. She wears a tunic made of
woven linen and soft leather blah blah
her skin is dusted, okay. Setting, a
hidden glit a hidden glade with an
ancient ancient
ancient enchanted forest towering
moss-covered trees, okay. Cathedral
branch into a twined canopy blah blah
blah.
Mhm.
Field of shot Okay, here it is. This is
what I'm trying to do.
A medium wide shot captures
So, I'm going to say here
a close-up
side
profile
shot.
You know what? Let's go to Let's go to
this. I'm going to say same thing.
I'm going to say same
character.
Okay?
So, look.
Character, setting, feel. Same character
but
different
setting
in the same world, though. That's
important. Same world
and
a
medium
close-up
shot
this time.
Shoot.
All right.
Let's send that prompt in. It's going to
rewrite it for us. Same character again.
Look, a cascading well blah with the
copper hair. Setting, a heart of
bustling
fay market? What the heck is a fay
market? F A E.
Uh nestle nestled in a grove ancient I'm
not going to read that. A medium
close-up shot and focus on the
character's face. All right, let's see
if I let's see what happens here. So, it
changed the two last pieces for us.
Okay, let's go back into the story.
Let's send that. Let's see what it
makes.
I think the bug
should turn into her.
What bug?
Oh, the little bug that we made before?
It'll make a great series. It would. I
think I That's exactly what I was
thinking when I first saw it.
All right, here's the second.
Oh, so she's in the market. It's like a
flea market.
So, look, it's the same character.
All right, so that's cool.
Let's see if there's anything changed.
Same thing, right? The staff looks the
same. Her hair looks the same.
Let me see one that's really close to
her.
I like that. I like this one.
Which one? Yes, that's that's the one.
This? This?
So, 1 2 3.
I like one.
No, I like Wait, which one did I like?
I forget now.
1 2 3 4.
2. I like two.
I like two. So, here we go. Use this
image.
This is the one.
So, now first frame is locked in.
I'm going to ask I'm going to ask Google
Gemini. Number two. Yeah, number two as
well. I picked that one.
Give me a short script
that she can say
during It takes me longer to prompt it
than to just type the script.
the scene.
This is for I'm going to just give it
context. Google
VO3
limited to 8 seconds.
All right, so I'm going to say just
with action and dialogue.
Give me a short script that with action
and dialogue that she can say during the
scene. Put it Uh this is for Google VO3
limited to 8 seconds. The young woman
Oh, why did you give me an image? I
don't want that.
Pushes past a shimmering curtain of
beads.
Like it doesn't know what it's doing.
It doesn't know about this scene right
here. See, it's not as smart as as
ChatGPT. ChatGPT is smart. It knows what
the heck happened before.
Gemini seems to be oblivious to what
happened before. I don't want any of
this. This is not work out. So, let's go
back to that scene.
Okay, so
she says
Welcome.
Yeah, I want to create my own script as
well, but I don't usually do, you know,
these AI scripts, but I do it for this
just because I don't feel like thinking
about it. Welcome to the
What's the place name again?
Wonderland.
Welcome to the Wonderland flea market.
Fairy market.
Just going to call it a fairy market.
Do you have a selection
of potions.
What else do they have?
Magical crafts
and the best
What else do they have here? The best
what?
Fairy dust.
in the land.
Cut to I'm going to do a scene where it
cuts to
um character interacting.
I want to see if it generates other
people in that world that looks like her
with vendors.
I would pushing it here.
Fairy dust. All right, cool. We said the
same thing. Welcome to the
Welcome to the Wonderland fairy market.
We have a selection of potions, magical
crafts, and the best fairy dust in the
land. Cut to character interacting with
vendors.
All right, fast frames. Send it.
All right. So, if you guys while this is
doing this, if you guys are interested
in taking a it's at this time at this
point is like an hour and a half almost
now.
Uh
everything that I teach you here for
free it's packaged in a deal where it's
a course and you can take it and also
join our community. So, if you already
have a a pro at this and you don't need
this the course, uh you would at least
benefit from being in the Discord group.
So, it's in my link is in the the link
is in bio.
It the price was just lowered to $24.99
and I also have a 15% off coupon that
you can use. It's in my bio right here
if you go to my TikTok page
and then click on this link,
you'll be able to log in to go see this
my course. First link.
And here it is. You can join it from
here. You can about all the benefits.
You can read all the reviews.
And that will give you access to our
Discord group, which is
um
almost 600 members and growing.
And this is where I share all the
updates. So, for example, we have
announcements.
Any bonus stuff that I add will be in
here.
Uh for example, this was when you can
make
people of all ages talk. So, here
uh I have updated the group about
there's no restriction. And this is when
This is on July 24th. And this is when
all those baby talk videos came about.
Once people realized that you can make
anybody talk
using text prompts, not videos. Uh not
image prompts. You can't upload a
picture of a of a minor and make them
talk. You can only do it if it's a
complete AI generation. I'm going to
play this one for you and then we we'll
go back to that video. It's probably
done by now. Jason, are you selling
stickers again during recess?
>> Inflation hitting hard, Ms. Janet. My
dad lost his job. Someone's got to
hustle. Jason, you're four.
Jason
Uh I had a hard time connecting Discord.
So, if you it's probably a local issue,
whether it's on your on your phone, on
your computer. If you did it on your
phone, try it from your computer and
vice versa. If it doesn't work, um
if it doesn't work, DM me here on TikTok
and I'll give you a an invite link.
A direct invite link to it. But, I like
you to connect it through better
because it will assign you the proper
roles automatically.
So, it'll give you like the premium
member role cuz if you don't have the
premium member role, a lot of these
channels will be hidden.
So, I like you to connect it through
better. If If you can't, um
just DM me here on TikTok or you can DM
me on Discord.
My Discord name is the same as my TikTok
name right here.
That's the Discord uh username if you
want to DM in there. But, only if you
have problems connecting it on a
computer or the phone vice versa.
It doesn't work if you already have
another connected.
Um I mean, I'm sorry. If you have
another
Discord connected, you have to make sure
that your WAP account has no Discords
connected at all.
All right, let's see what happens here.
Welcome everybody. Welcome in.
Welcome to the Wonderland Fairy Market.
We have a selection of potions, magical
crafts, and the best fairy dust in the
land.
Welcome to the Wonderland Fairy Market.
>> Nice. We have a selection of potions,
magical crafts, and the best fairy dust
in the
Where did that thing come from, her
hand?
>> best best fairy dust
in the
land. So So, her staff turned into
money.
>> crafts and Her staff turned into
something that she handed to the lady
somehow.
>> in the
Yeah, so this one you know, I don't know
if anybody would catch that, but
>> and the best fairy dust in the land. You
don't have to do this cut two scenes. I
just did I just do it just to push it to
make it more
you know, well, there's some people in
the back here. Just to give us some more
diversity, but if you want to keep it
safe,
all you have to do is that don't put cut
to it at the end. Just put that just to
say this, we have the best selection of
potion magical crafts in the best fairy
dust in the land, and it would have been
the whole time just like this.
>> a selection of potions, magical crafts,
and the best fairy dust in the land.
That That would make a great series,
right?
Welcome to the magical land of
Wonderland, where anything is possible.
Welcome to the Wonderland Fairy Market.
So, her ears are out before, but not
here, right? So, that was my problem
because I should have picked the first
frame.
I didn't realize the ears are sticking
out here, and here they're hiding.
She put her hair back, all right?
She put her hair back. So, that's how
you do it. So, you just have to make
sure the character doesn't look like a
little thing like this, you know.
See, all because you asked that
question, we would have did a whole
different turn right here.
We would have been talking about
something else, but I like I like just
interacting live with some people and
just getting cuz I don't have an agenda
other than just showing you prompts, and
this shows it to you anyway.
This shows you that it it does it it the
point comes across here.
So, that's what I have here for the live
today. We've been on for almost 2 hours.
Uh if you guys don't follow me yet, just
a reminder to hit that follow button.
Oh, we have an hour and a half.
Maybe I can go for a little bit longer
than I thought it was 2 hours now. So,
we have an hour and 35 minutes. We go a
little longer.
Make it where everyone can subscribe to
what?
The Discord server?
Yeah, the Discord server used to be
open, but then I closed it cuz it I got
a lot of random people in there, and if
you don't put a paid wall on your
Discord,
uh you get like scammers, you get like
some people will still pay and then get
get their way in and try to like scam
people and whatever.
Um
the cartoon series?
Oh, yeah, you talking about the cartoon.
I thought you were talking about the
Discord. Yeah, but the Discord server is
closed to only uh paid members of the
course because it filters out a lot of
uh nonsense.
It used to be open before before I had
the course, but once I had the had the
course in there, I I locked it up to
only members.
Let's see if there's anything else here
that I want to share from the Discord. I
think everything else is good.
Covered pretty much everything that I
wanted to cover.
And let's see.
So, if you guys are wondering like if
you
if you want to make like fancier things,
like for example, a commercial like
this. I don't know if you have a a
purpose for something like this. For
example,
like watch this.
Like I said, I don't know if you have a
purpose for this. I don't I don't want
to show things that are just no purpose
to it, but if you do, I can't think of
one that you would have unless you're
making commercials for Tesla and stuff
like this one.
But this was all done using a JSON
prompt, okay? And the JSON prompt works
like this. I have a a JSON bot that I
created. It's a GPT It's a chat GPT bot
essentially, okay?
It's DJI VL 3 center prompter. It
creates more things cinematic, so
My character gives weather and health
tips. Nice. I should definitely create
something.
I'm going to open up your page here.
I'll save it. Um
So, there's my GPT bot, okay? So, here
you can ask it to make, for example,
make me a
commercial What's it called?
for
um
a
an animate I don't know if it's going to
work at all. I don't even know what what
I want from this, but make me a
commercial for an animated
character
that
gives weather
What did you say? Weather and health?
Weather That's That's That's um
health tips.
Those are Those are two different
categories. How does that work?
Health and weather.
Like, "Hey, it's sunny out. Go run."
I don't even know what what what I want
from this, but I just typed it see if
I've having problems with chat GPT
today. I need my cache is probably
clogged up cuz look, when I put a prompt
it it's not responding to me today.
It only works if I delete if I close the
browser.
I When this happens, it's something to
do with your local it's like a local
issue.
Your computer cache is full or something
like that.
Like you need to clean some of the
stuff.
Let me try it. Oh, it did work. Shoot.
All right, so I did it twice.
All right, hold on one second.
All right, so it's back. I just have to
refresh it.
All right, so it did work. I sent it
twice by mistake. So here, let's copy
this. This is a for the character. So,
make me a commercial for an animated
character that gives weather and health
tips, okay?
Let's go to flow.
Right in here, we're going to paste that
JSON prompt.
Text to video.
We're going to change this to V03 fast.
I don't even know what's going to
happen.
I'm just going to blindly send it.
Oh, I make different videos for both.
Oh, this one's going to be one for both.
This one's going to be one video for
both topics. So, let's see.
Dream light productions, how you doing?
You caught me at the end of the live
here. I want to see what this comes up
with.
And I think this is going to be it for
me today.
Welcome in, folks. Welcome in. Thanks
for the likes. Thanks for the likes. We
got past 10,000 likes. Appreciate that.
And as soon as this is done, I'm going
to bid farewell to my YouTube audience,
and then I'll stay here on TikTok for a
little bit longer.
So, if you're watching on YouTube, I'm
making this using the JSON bot that I
just showed you.
It pretty much creates something you can
read all this. It's It's in my This is
free for you to use. I opened it up not
just for course members but for anybody.
The link is in my bio. The link is in
the bio. So, if you go to my link tree
where all my links are,
this is what it looks like right here.
If you click right there if you're on
TikTok. On YouTube it will be in the
video description. And right here it's
called a free cinematic prompter GPT. If
you're watching this later in a recorded
video.
There is an animated character. She
talks about weather.
Let's play it.
I don't even know what this is going to
do at all.
It might be really really bad but who
knows.
The GPT wasn't built for this. It's
built for cinematic prompts like
commercials
and films not um some random idea that I
just put in there combining two
different topics.
So, that's an intro. That could be the
intro for the show.
She goes outside.
And then you got your health tips and
your you know, it's interesting how it
did all that.
So, that can be like, you know,
Michelle's tips comes up on the screen
in logo and letters.
It does Yeah, so this is a it's built to
be a cinematic uh it's called a
cinematic prompter. You You can read all
about it here.
But it's not built to create like
animated stuff at all. So, here we can
put like um make me
a
um
What kind of commercial do we want? Make
me a
um
I don't know.
truck commercial
I'm going to say make me a super truck
commercial.
So, there you go. It's going to make it.
We're going to copy it.
And
we're going to paste it right in here.
Text to video, VO3 fast.
Send it.
I haven't read anything, but it's it's
meant for you to use it to be more
specific. It's made for you to So,
essentially what it's going to do is
it's going to add like uh
camera styles, lighting styles. It's
going to add details that you wouldn't
otherwise think of. So, it's made to be
more specific. So, this is what I want
you to put in there if you're going to
use it. Look, what would be helpful for
me to know? Meaning the bot, okay? You
want to give it a prompt, meaning tell
it the character, the setting, the shot
composition, the action, and the
dialogue. Tell it that. Tell it this if
and then anything else here, it's going
to fill in for you unless you tell it.
So, it's going to do the style for you.
It's going to do the camera movement.
It's going to do the lighting. And I
give you some here of what some
languages that you can use, some
vocabulary you can use to describe
the style, the camera, the lighting.
If you don't describe it, if you don't
write the prompt yourself, like I like
writing my own prompts. If you don't
describe it, it's going to make
that for you. That's the point of the
bot. And if you do describe it
perfectly, everything that you want,
it's going to add more cinematic tones
to it, if that makes sense. That's why
the that's called the cinema prompter.
It's making cinematic things.
So, we can close this, right? We can
close the GPT. Oh, no, let's leave it up
before next time.
Here we go. This is a super truck
commercial that I just asked for it to
make. Let's play it.
Luis, thank you for the gift. What?
Somebody gave you a gift? Somebody gave
me a gift?
What is going on with the gift comment?
I'm not sure.
The last gift I see is from Sky Sky
Flutters, which I thanked her for. So,
I'm not sure which one.
DJ KO KO
Mason, that's a nice name, Mason. Where
are you from, Mason?
Mason is from South Carolina, I think.
He sounds like he's from South Carolina.
He looks like it. Look, I see his image
right here. He's a good country boy.
He's from Uganda. Okay, never mind.
All right, let's play it. Let's play the
Let's play the video.
So, you see all that? Just came from one
prompt that said, "Make me a a super
truck commercial."
And I could have added more, but because
I was so vague, it didn't really, you
know.
But, that's great that you can just get
that just from writing that one prompt.
All right, so we we covered a lot today.
We covered how to make animated
characters. We talked about how to use
Gemini to create your images. We even
went over some of my older prompts that
I built here for you guys. Like again,
if you like this stuff, make sure you
subscribe. Um if you're watching here on
YouTube or if you watch it on TikTok,
follow the account. Thank you for the
gifts, guys, and all the people that
gave the gifts that are already gone,
but they did come through with some even
a galaxy. I got my first galaxy today,
folks.
This is Google Flow. And if you guys
want to learn more about it, you can
catch my lives here
um weekdays, Monday, Tuesday, not
Wednesdays, but Monday, Tuesday,
Thursday, Fridays at 3:00 p.m. Eastern
Standard Time. And I'm using Google
Flow, which is a service provided by
Google AI Pro that you can try out for
the first month for free. And if you
guys are
beginners or you just have problems with
uh writing your prompts and you need
more help, I do have a course. Go to the
link in my bio, which is right here. You
can use the code DJI15 for 15% off.
And that is the information about the
course. That promo code no longer works.
It's a
old promo code, so I got to change that.
It's
It's DJI 15 now. So, that one's
That one is when the course was much
more expensive. So, that's not going to
work and it's used up. So, I got to fix
that. But, that is the course. It's
DJI 15 for 15% off, okay?
The course used to be $34.99.
And then we used to do a 50% off code on
this, but this this expired. So, don't
use that one.
For 15% off.
I put that in the chat here on TikTok.
So, guys, thank you so much. Be sure to
follow if you don't already. Thanks for
the gifts. Thanks for the interactions.
And I'll see you guys next time. Be sure
to look at some of my videos if you
haven't already. Go like some of the
stuff. Comment that you came from the
lives. Like that, you can get more stuff
out. I can get my stuff out to more
people cuz that lately my my videos
haven't been reaching that much. I'm not
sure why.
But, um pretty much doing the same
things that I did when I used to get
millions of views on them. So, like for
example, right here.
I I guess it's just an algorithm thing,
but it does help if you guys go on there
and like it as well. So, thank you for
your help. Thank you. No problem.
And I'll see you guys